<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Jan de Muijnck-Hughes</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Jan de Muijnck-Hughes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Big Image Sample</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2017-03-07-bigimg-sample/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2017-03-07-bigimg-sample/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The image banners at the top of the page are refered to as &amp;ldquo;bigimg&amp;rdquo; in this theme. They are optional, and one more more can be specified. If more than one is specified, the images rotate every 10 seconds. In the front matter, bigimgs are specified using an array of hashes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Sample</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2017-03-05-math-sample/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2017-03-05-math-sample/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;KaTeX can be used to generate complex math formulas server-side.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\phi = \frac{(1+\sqrt{5})}{2} = 1.6180339887\cdots
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additional details can be found on &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Khan/KaTeX&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt; or on the &lt;a href=&#34;http://tiddlywiki.com/plugins/tiddlywiki/katex/&#34;&gt;Wiki&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code Sample</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2016-03-08-code-sample/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2016-03-08-code-sample/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The following are two code samples using syntax highlighting.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flake it till you make it</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2015-02-26-flake-it-till-you-make-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2015-02-26-flake-it-till-you-make-it/</guid>
      <description>Under what circumstances should we step off a path? When is it essential that we finish what we start? If I bought a bag of peanuts and had an allergic reaction, no one would fault me if I threw it out. If I ended a relationship with a woman who hit me, no one would say that I had a commitment problem. But if I walk away from a seemingly secure route because my soul has other ideas, I am a flake?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test markdown</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2015-02-20-test-markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2015-02-20-test-markdown/</guid>
      <description>You can write regular markdown here and Hugo will automatically convert it to a nice webpage. I strongly encourage you to take 5 minutes to learn how to write in markdown - it&amp;rsquo;ll teach you how to transform regular text into bold/italics/headings/tables/etc.
Here is some bold text
Here is a secondary heading Here&amp;rsquo;s a useless table:
Number Next number Previous number Five Six Four Ten Eleven Nine Seven Eight Six Two Three One How about a yummy crepe?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To be</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2015-02-13-hamlet-monologue/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2015-02-13-hamlet-monologue/</guid>
      <description>To be, or not to be&amp;ndash;that is the question: Whether &amp;rsquo;tis nobler in the mind to suffer The slings and arrows of outrageous fortune Or to take arms against a sea of troubles And by opposing end them. To die, to sleep&amp;ndash; No more&amp;ndash;and by a sleep to say we end The heartache, and the thousand natural shocks That flesh is heir to. &amp;lsquo;Tis a consummation Devoutly to be wished. To die, to sleep&amp;ndash; To sleep&amp;ndash;perchance to dream: ay, there&amp;rsquo;s the rub, For in that sleep of death what dreams may come When we have shuffled off this mortal coil, Must give us pause.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dear diary</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2015-01-27-dear-diary/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2015-01-27-dear-diary/</guid>
      <description>What is it with that Mary girl? Dragging me to school every day. As if I had a choice. What you don&amp;rsquo;t hear in those nursery rhymes is that she starves me if I don&amp;rsquo;t go to school with her; it&amp;rsquo;s the only way I can stay alive! I&amp;rsquo;m thinking about being adopted by Little Bo Peep, sure I may get lost, but anything is better than being with Mary and those little brats at school (shudder, shudder).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soccer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2015-01-19-soccer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2015-01-19-soccer/</guid>
      <description>From Wikipedia:
Association football, more commonly known as football or soccer,[2] is a sport played between two teams of eleven players with a spherical ball. It is played by 250 million players in over 200 countries, making it the world&amp;rsquo;s most popular sport.[3][4][5][6] The game is played on a rectangular field with a goal at each end. The object of the game is to score by getting the ball into the opposing goal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pirates arrrr</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2015-01-15-pirates/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2015-01-15-pirates/</guid>
      <description>Piracy is typically an act of robbery or criminal violence at sea. The term can include acts committed on land, in the air, or in other major bodies of water or on a shore. It does not normally include crimes committed against persons traveling on the same vessel as the perpetrator (e.g. one passenger stealing from others on the same vessel). The term has been used throughout history to refer to raids across land borders by non-state agents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First post!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2015-01-04-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2015-01-04-first-post/</guid>
      <description>This is my first post, how exciting!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First post!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/thesis/2015-01-04-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/thesis/2015-01-04-first-post/</guid>
      <description>This is my first post, how exciting!
urg</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Engineering Should be TyDe!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/page/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/page/research/</guid>
      <description>Interests Generally speaking, I am interested in how we can take state-of-the-art advances in programming language theory, namely type-systems &amp;amp; functional programming, and use these advances to fundamentally change how we design systems to make them more trustworthy: Secure and Safe.
Specifically, I am interested in bettering system design and construction through applications of:
functional programming; formal verification; mathematically informed programming; dependent types; sub-structural typing (quantitative, resource-dependent, session); and algebraic effect handlers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/page/service/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/page/service/</guid>
      <description>Programme Committees I have served as a committee member on the following committees:
20th Asian Symposium on Programming Languages and Systems APLAS 2022 33rd Symposium on Implementation and Application of Functional Languages IFL21 9th Workshop on Mathematically Structured Functional Programming, MSFP 2022 Artefact Reviewing For the following artefact evaluation committees:
I have co-chaired the:
20th Asian Symposium on Programming Languages and Systems APLAS AEC 2022. I have served as committee member on:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/page/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/page/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Details of duties performed during my tenure as an academic. Module descriptions are available from the respective University&amp;rsquo;s course catalogues.
University of Glasgow At Glasgow I am involved with a variety of teaching duties at Level 4, and Masters Level.
2020-2021 CS4025P: Individual Project Supervisor to two Level 4 Student. 2019-2020 CS4025P: Individual Project Supervisor to one Level 4 Student. 2018-2019 CS4025P: Individual Project Supervisor to two Level 4 Students. CS4021: Functional Programming with Haskell Co-Lecturer, and tutor on course&amp;rsquo;s corresponding MOOC.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
